=Revenge of Royal Princess=
= انتقام الأميرة الملكية =
=Episode 13=
= الحلقة 13 =
I want her.
أريدها.
No way.
مستحيل.
Your Majesty, are you trying to break your promise?
جلالة الملك ، هل تحاول أن تخل بوعدك؟
Well.
نحن سوف.
You should try.
يجب أن تحاول.
If you can beat Han Shu,
إذا تمكنت من التغلب على هان شو ،
I will let you go.
سوف اتركك تذهب.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You know Miss Xie can't make it.
أنت تعلم أن الآنسة شيه لا تستطيع فعل ذلك.
Save it.
احفظها.
Yes.
نعم.
Royal Princess.
أميرة ملكية.
Three arrows and ten rings.
ثلاثة سهام وعشر حلقات.
You!
أنت!
You said you can't shoot arrows.
قلت أنه لا يمكنك إطلاق السهام.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I have a grievance.
لدي شكوى.
Your Majesty, please uphold justice for me.
جلالة الملك ، أرجو أن تحافظ على العدل من أجلي.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
This wicked woman
هذه المرأة الشريرة
murdered my son.
قتل ابني.
Please put her to execution
من فضلك ضعها في الإعدام
and uphold justice
وإعلاء العدالة
for the Gu family and my son.
لعائلة غو وابني.
If you want to hurt her,
إذا كنت تريد أن تؤذيها ،
ask for my opinion first.
اسأل عن رأيي أولا.
Gu Yan bought an official and deceived the emperor,
اشترت قو يان مسؤولاً وخدعت الإمبراطور ،
he should have been executed long ago.
كان يجب أن يتم إعدامه منذ فترة طويلة.
Your Royal Highness.
صاحب السمو الملكي.
I want to make a deal with you.
اريد ان ابرم صفقة معك.
I'd like to trade myself
أود أن أتاجر بنفسي
for a chance of life.
للحصول على فرصة الحياة.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Recently,
مؤخرا،
the Gu family will come to file an imperial appeal.
ستأتي عائلة غو لتقديم استئناف إمبراطوري.
If you can save me,
إذا كنت تستطيع إنقاذي ،
I am yours.
أنا لك.
Gu Yan
قو يان
tricked me into taking service for three years
خدعتني لأخذ الخدمة لمدة ثلاث سنوات
in exchange for fame.
مقابل الشهرة.
Yet he was having fun with another woman at home.
ومع ذلك ، كان يستمتع مع امرأة أخرى في المنزل.
How dare the Gu family
كيف تجرؤ عائلة جو
sue me?
قاضيني؟
You wicked woman!
أنت امرأة شريرة!
How dare you
كيف تجرؤ
trample on the majesty of the royal family at will?
تدوس على جلالة العائلة المالكة في الإرادة؟
Pass on my decree.
تمرير مرسوم بلدي.
The Gu family deceived the subordinates and superiors to obtain official positions.
خدعت عائلة قو مرؤوسيهم ورؤسائهم للحصول على مناصب رسمية.
Search their house and confiscate their property.
ابحث في منزلهم وصادر ممتلكاتهم.
Xie Yugui followed my will
اتبع Xie Yugui إرادتي
to eradicate traitors for the country.
للقضاء على الخونة للوطن.
Reward her.
كافئها.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
شكرا لك جلالة الملك.
Your Majesty, please find out the truth.
جلالة الملك ، من فضلك اكتشف الحقيقة.
Go.
اذهب.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Your Majesty, we are wronged.
جلالة الملك ، نحن مظلومون.
She never dressed like this.
لم تلبس مثل هذا قط.
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(تنتمي حصريًا إلى Tencent.)